我在準備放手，讓他們接手
I'm letting it go, and letting them in
正思考著要怎麼重起
pondering for a way to begin
乾乾淨淨，俐俐落落
coming out clean, cleaning up nice
我在準備改變，讓他們幫我
They're shaping me up and taking me in
撫平傷痛並帶我向前
forgiving my pain and riding the wind
是否回家就會改變一切
Will everything change when we arrive?
星群墜落，前所未有的快
The stars are falling faster than before
月亮招喚，但地球招更猛
The moon is calling, but earth is calling more
喔哦，噢
Whoa, ohhh
現在是否看清？
now can't ya see?
喔哦，噢
Whoa, ohhh
自由真是清新
so good to be free
喔哦
Whoa
我不需要任何東西
I don't need anything
因為我就—
because I'm just,
—就已經是我自己
I'm just who I want to be
就是自己
I'm just me
在太空中，是真的孤獨
It's terribly lonely out in space
很少笑聲，笑容抹滅
laughter is rare, and smiles erased
朋友消失，噢，我是怎樣？
friendship is gone; oh, what had I done?
但，我學到教訓，不會跑掉
But, now that I've learned, I'll stay for a while
我已經飛了一千里遠
now that I've burned ten-hundred miles
我不會再來，不怎麼好玩
I'll never go back, it wasn't much fun
太陽落下，前所未有的快
The sun is setting faster than before
生命招喚，就在我家門口
But life is stirring just outside the door
喔哦，噢
Whoa, ohhh
現在是否看清？
now can't ya see?
喔哦，噢
Whoa, ohhh
自由真是清新
so good to be free
喔哦
Whoa
我不需要任何東西
I don't need anything
因為我就—
because I'm just,
—就已經是我自己
I'm just who I want to be
就是自己...
I'm just me...
喔哦...
Whoa...
噢...
Oooh...
喔哦，噢
Whoa, ohhh
現在是否看清？
now can't ya see?
喔哦，噢
Whoa, ohhh
自由真是清新
so good to be free
喔哦
Whoa
我不需要任何東西
I don't need anything
因為我就—
because I'm just,
—就已經是我自己
I'm just who I want to be
就是自己
I'm just me